{
   "Questions":
   [
      {
         "QuestionText": "How old is Roger Federer?",
         "Answers": [
            "35 years old",
            "37 years old",
            "39 years old",
            "41 years old"
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 2,
         "Tags": [
            "Federer",
            "ATP",
            "Tennis"
         ]
      },
      {
         "QuestionText": "What is Brad Gilbert's nickname for Kei Nishikori?",
         "Answers": [
            "Silent K",
            "Special K",
            "Stupid K",
            "Smelly K"
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 1,
         "Tags": [
            "ATP",
            "Commentators",
            "Random Trivia",
            "Tennis"
         ]
      },
      {
         "QuestionText": "What was the first ATP title that Jannik Sinner won?",
         "Answers": [
            "Sofia Open",
            "ATP NextGen",
            "St. Petersburg Open",
            "Hamburg European Open"
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 0,
         "Tags": [
            "ATP",
            "Tennis"
         ]
      },
      {
         "QuestionText": "Alex Dogopolov got bitten by what breed of cat?",
         "Answers": [
            "Serval Cat",
            "Sphinx Cat",
            "Servil Cat",
            "Stupid Cat"
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 0,
         "Tags": [
            "Random Trivia",
            "ATP",
            "Tennis"
         ]
      },
      {
         "QuestionText": "Who won the 2020 US Open?",
         "Answers": [
            "Alex Zverev",
            "Dominic Thiem",
            "Novak Djokovic",
            "Roger Federer"
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 1,
         "Tags": [
            "ATP",
            "Tennis",
            "Grand Slams"
         ]
      },
      {
         "QuestionText": "When did Rafael Nadal turn pro?",
         "Answers": [
            2002,
            2000,
            2001,
            2003
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 2,
         "Tags": [
            "ATP",
            "Tennis",
            "Nadal"
         ]
      },
      {
         "QuestionText": "How many slams has Marin Cilic won?",
         "Answers": [
            0,
            5,
            2,
            1
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 3,
         "Tags": [
            "ATP",
            "Tennis",
            "Grand Slams"
         ]
      },
      {
         "QuestionText": "Who won Indian Wells in 2018?",
         "Answers": [
            "Roger Federer",
            "Rafael Nadal",
            "Juan Martin Del Potro",
            "Novak Djokovic"
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 2,
         "Tags": [
            "ATP",
            "Tennis",
            "Masters"
         ]
      },
      {
         "QuestionText": "Where was Cameron Norrie born?",
         "Answers": [
            "Johannesburg, South Africa",
            "Yaound√©, Cameroon",
            "London, Great Britian",
            "Accra, Ghana"
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 0,
         "Tags": [
            "ATP",
            "Tennis",
            "Random Trivia"
         ]
      },
      {
         "QuestionText": "How fast was the world's fastest Grand Slam final?",
         "Answers": [
            "32 mins",
            "34 mins",
            "33 mins",
            "31 mins"
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 0,
         "Tags": [
            "Grand Slams",
            "Tennis",
            "Random Trivia"
         ]
      },
      {
         "QuestionText": "Which of these players has completed a Calendar Grand Slam",
         "Answers": [
            "Daniel Buge",
            "Don Budge",
            "Dan Burgel",
            "Dom Budgel"
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 1,
         "Tags": [
            "Grand Slams",
            "Tennis",
            "Random Trivia"
         ]
      },
      {
         "QuestionText": "Alex de Minaur has citizenship in Austrailia and what?",
         "Answers": [
            "France",
            "Italy",
            "Spain",
            "Poland"
         ],
         "CorrectAnswerIndex": 2,
         "Tags": [
            "ATP",
            "Tennis",
            "Random Trivia"
         ]
      }
   ]
}